<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Motion Layout</string>
    <string name="motionlayout_is_a_layout_type_that_helps_you_manage_motion_and_widget_animation_in_your_app_motionlayout_is_a_subclass_of_constraintlayout_and_builds_upon_its_rich_layout_capabilities_as_part_of_the_constraintlayout_library_motionlayout_is_available_as_a_support_library_and_is_backwards_compatible_to_api_level_14_let_us_take_care_of_you_we_offer_assistance_at_the_airport_on_the_plane_and_upon_arrival_for_a_variety_of_needs_including_traveling_with_devices_disabilities_children_and_more_we_can_help_you_if_you_ve_lost_an_item_on_a_plane_or_in_an_american_operated_area_at_the_airport_or_at_a_security_checkpoint_visit_our_lost_and_found_page_and_we_ll_point_you_in_the_right_direction_bag_delivery_service_bypass_baggage_claim_whether_you_re_traveling_for_business_or_pleasure_on_your_next_trip_let_us_bring_your_bags_to_you_first_checked_bag_free_on_domestic_itineraries_earn_50_000_bonus_miles_your_first_checked_bag_is_free_on_domestic_itineraries_for_you_and_up_to_4_travel_companions_with_the_citi_aadvantage_platinum_select_card_terms_apply_special_items_and_sports_equipment_from_musical_instruments_to_military_bags_here_s_everything_you_need_to_know_traveling_with_pets_we_re_making_your_pet_our_priority_here_are_some_guidelines_to_help_make_your_journey_smootherit_is_a_1_minute_typing_test_program_to_test_your_typing_speed_and_skill_in_this_application_you_can_perform_a_complete_typing_test_in_1_minute">MotionLayout is a layout type that helps you manage motion and widget animation in your app. MotionLayout is a subclass of ConstraintLayout and builds upon its rich layout capabilities. As part of the ConstraintLayout library, MotionLayout is available as a support library and is backwards-compatible to API level 14 Let us take care of you We offer assistance at the airport, on the plane and upon arrival for a variety of needs including traveling with devices, disabilities, children and more.We can help you If you’ve lost an item on a plane or in an American-operated area, at the airport or at a security checkpoint, visit our lost and found page and we’ll point you in the right direction.Bag delivery service Bypass baggage claim Whether you\'re traveling for business or pleasure on your next trip, let us bring your bags to you.First checked bag free on domestic itineraries Earn 50,000 bonus miles Your first checked bag is free on domestic itineraries for you and up to 4 travel companions with the Citi® / AAdvantage® Platinum Select® card. Terms apply.Special items and sports equipment From musical instruments to military bags, here\'s everything you need to know.Traveling with pets We’re making your pet our priority. Here are some guidelines to help make your journey smootherIt is a 1 minute typing test program to test your typing speed and skill. In this application, you can perform a complete typing test in 1 minute.</string>
</resources>